hackathon.com 2018-11-25

# BeMyApp Cookies Policy

**Service**

Service is the bemyapp.com website operated by BeMyApp.

 **Personal Data**

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession). 

**Usage Data**

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit). 

**Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your device (computer or mobile device). 

**Data Controller**

Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data. 

 **Data Processors (or Service Providers)**

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller. We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively. 

 **Data Subject (or User)**

Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data.

Last updated: May 24, 2018

Protecting your private information is our priority.

BeMyApp, with its affiliates and its subsidiaries (collectively, “BeMyApp”, "us", "we", or "our") owns, operates or provides access to several interactive websites, mobile and connected applications, and other online interactive features and services, including, but not limited to, emails, newsletters, chat areas, forums, communities, sweepstakes and contests (collectively “Services”). This Privacy Policy applies to all information collected about you by BeMyApp, regardless of how it is collected or stored, and describes, among other things, the types of information collected about you when you interact with the Services, how your information may be used, when your information may be disclosed, how you can control the use and disclosure of your information, and how your information is protected. This Privacy Policy covers information collected through the following websites and mobile applications 

  * Bemyapp.com 
  * Hackerunit.com
  * Coderpower.com
  * Hackathon.com
  * Virtualconference.com
  * Withthebest.com
  * Hackerbucks.com  

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. 

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from our Services. 

Except as otherwise noted in this Privacy Policy, BeMyApp is a data controller (as that term is used under the EU General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR")), which means that we decide how and why the information you provide to us is processed. This Policy may be amended or updated from time to time to reflect changes in our practices with respect to the Processing of your information, or changes in applicable law. We encourage you to read this Policy carefully, and to regularly check this page to review any changes we might make. 

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you. 

**Types of Data Collected**

 **Personal Data**

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to: 

  * Email address
  * First name and last name 
  * Company, position and skills 
  * Phone number 
  * Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City 
  * Cookies and Usage Data   

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send. You can also unsubscribe, delete, modify and download your data anytime at [data.bemyapp.com](http://data.bemyapp.com/). 

**Usage Data**

We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data. 

**Location Data**

We may use and store information about your location if you give us permission to do so (“Location Data”). We use this data to provide features of our Service, to improve and customize our Service. You can enable or disable location services when you use our Service at any time, through your device settings.

 **Tracking Cookies Data**

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service. 

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use: 

  * Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.   

  * Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.   

  * Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.   

BeMyApp uses the collected data for various purposes: 

  * To provide and maintain our Service
  * To notify you about changes to our Service
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
  * To provide customer support 
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
  * To monitor the usage of our Service To detect, prevent and address technical issues 
  * To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information 

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), BeMyApp legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it. BeMyApp may process your Personal Data because: 

  * We need to perform a contract with you   

  * You have given us permission to do so 
  * The processing is in our legitimate interests
  * It's not overridden by your rights 
  * For payment processing purposes 
  * To comply with the law 

BeMyApp will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies. 

BeMyApp will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods. 

Because of the international nature of our business, we may need to transfer your Personal Data within the BeMyApp group of companies, and to third parties as noted in our [Sub-Processors](http://privacy.bemyapp.com/sub-processors) section, in connection with the purposes set out in this Policy. For this reason, we may transfer your Personal Data to other countries that may have different laws and data protection compliance requirements to those that apply in the country in which you are located. 

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

BeMyApp will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information. 

**Business Transaction**

If BeMyApp is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

 **Disclosure for Law Enforcement**

Under certain circumstances, BeMyApp may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

 **Legal Requirements**

BeMyApp may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: 

  * To comply with a legal obligation  

  * To protect and defend the rights or property of BeMyApp
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. 

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser. 

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. BeMyApp aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data. You can access, modify and download your data anytime at [data.bemyapp.com](http://data.bemyapp.com/).

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us. 

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights: 

**The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you.** You can access, update or delete your Personal Data directly either within your account settings section of the Services or on [data.bemyapp.com](http://data.bemyapp.com/). If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you. 

**The right of rectification.** You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete. 

 **The right to object.** You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.  
 **The right of restriction.**  You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information. 

 **The right to data portability.** You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.

 **The right to withdraw consent.** You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where BeMyApp relied on your consent to process your personal information. 

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests. 

You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA). 

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. 

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. 

You can access the list of Service Providers on our [Sub-Processors](http://privacy.bemyapp.com/sub-processors) section.

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. 

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services. 

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children"). 

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. 

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy. 

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us: 

  * By email: [privacy@bemyapp.com ](mailto:privacy@bemyapp.com)
